Guide to the University of Utah football video collection 1948-1999
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
University of Utah football video collection
1948-1999
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 (801) 581-8864
A0319
University of Utah
1,542 16mm films, 7 8mm films, 4 U-matic videocassettes, 1 Betacam videocassette, and 543 VHS videocassettes, many with copies available on DVD or Mini-DV.
The University of Utah Football video collection (1948-1999) contains footage of University of Utah football games, most of which are silent coach's films of games divided into separate reels for offense, defense and kicking.
Historical Note
The University of Utah Utes football team was founded in 1892. The team has won 12 of its 16 National Collegiate Athelitcs Association (NCAA) bowl games 1939-2010 and has played in the following conferences:
1910–1937: Rocky Mountain Athletic Conference
1938–1947: Big Seven Conference
1948–1961: Skyline Conference
1962–1998: Western Athletic Conference (WAC)
1999–2010: Mountain West Conference
2011–: Pacific-12 Conference (Pac-12)
The University of Utah Football video collection (1948-2003) contains footage of University of Utah football games, most of which are silent coaches' training films of games divided into separate reels for offense, defense and kicking.
The majority of the materials are arranged chronologically and by format.
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
Sports; NCAA football; Football--History; Sports and Recreation; Moving Images; Moving images
- Coach's films: games, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Utah vs. Oregon State, 1968 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 1-4)
    Reels 1-4, 2-4, 3-4, 4-4
  - Utah vs. Oregon State defense, 1968 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 5-7)
    Reels 1-3, 2-3, 3-3
  - Utah vs. Oregon State offense, 1968 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 8-9)
    Reels 1-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Washington State defense, 1968 October 05; 16mm film (Reel 10-11)
    Reels 1-3, 2-3
  - Utah vs. Washington State offense, 1968 October 05; 16mm film (Reel 12-14)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico, 1968 October 12; 16mm film (Reel 15-19)
    Reels 1-5, 2-5, 3-5, 4-5, 5-5
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1968 October 12; 16mm film (Reel 20)
    Reel 1-3
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1968 October 12; 16mm film (Reel 21-22)
    Reels 2-3, 3-3
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1968 October 19; 16mm film (Reel 23-24)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1968 October 19; 16mm film (Reel 25-27)
  - Utah vs. Oregon, 1968 October 26; 16mm film (Reel 28-30)
    Reels 2-4, 3-4, 4-4
- Coach's films: games, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Utah vs. Oregon offense, 1968 October 26; 16mm film (Reel 31-33)
  - Utah vs. Oregon defense, 1968 October 26; 16mm film (Reel 34-35)
  - Utah vs. Brigham Young University (BYU) offense, 1968 November 02; 16mm film (Reel 36-37)
  - Utah vs. Brigham Young University (BYU) defense, 1968 November 02; 16mm film (Reel 38)
    Reel 3-3
  - Utah vs. Brigham Young University (BYU) color, 1968 November 02; 16mm film (Reel 39)
    Reel 1-4
  - Utah vs. Arizona offense, 1968 November 16; 16mm film (Reel 40-42)
  - Utah vs. Arizona defense, 1968 November 16; 16mm film (Reel 43-45)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1968 November 23; 16mm film (Reel 46-47)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1968 November 23; 16mm film (Reel 48-49)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1969 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 50)
    Reel 1-2
  - Utah vs. Oregon State, 1969 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 51)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1969 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 52)
    Reel 2-2
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1969 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 53-54)
  - Training film: Inside defense, 1969; 16mm film (Reel 55)
- Coach's films: spring practice, 1969-1971 (Box 3)
  - University of Utah spring football, 1969 May 09; 16mm film (Reel 56)
    Reel 2-4
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1969 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 57)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1969 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 58)
    Reel 5-5
  - Training film: San Jose State pass offense, 1969; 16mm film (Reel 59)
  - Training film: Spread punt protection, 1969; 16mm film (Reel 60)
  - Training film: Defensive punt rushes, 1969; 16mm film (Reel 61)
  - Training film: Draw and tackle trap vs. University of Texas El Paso (UTEP), 1969; 16mm film (Reel 62)
  - University of Utah first spring scrimmage, 1971 April 10; 16mm film (Reel 63)
  - University of Utah spring game, 1971 April 10; 16mm film (Reel 64-65)
    Reels 3-4, 4-4
- Coach's films: spring practice, games, 1970 (Box 4)
  - University of Utah first spring scrimmage, 1970 April 18; 16mm film (Reel 66)
  - University of Utah freshman scrimmage, 1970; 16mm film (Reel 67)
    Reel 1
  - University of Utah spring game, 1970 May 13; 16mm film (Reel 68-69)
  - University of Utah fall scrimmage, 1970 September 12; 16mm film (Reel 70-73)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1970 September 19; 16mm film (Reel 74-78)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1970 September 19; 16mm film (Reel 79-81)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1970 September 19; 16mm film (Reel 82-84)
  - Utah vs. UTEP pass formations and patterns, 1970 September 19; 16mm film (Reel 85)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1970 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 86-88)
    Reels 1-3 2-3, 3-3
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1970 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 89-90)
- Coach's films: games, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1970 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 91)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico pass formations and patterns, 1970 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 92)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico, 1970 September 26; 16mm film (Reel 93-97)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State defense, 1970 October 03; 16mm film (Reel 98)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State offense, 1970 October 03; 16mm film (Reel 99-100)
  - Utah vs. Oregon State offense, 1970 October 10; 16mm film (Reel 101-102)
  - Utah vs. Oregon State defense, 1970 October 10; 16mm film (Reel 103-105)
  - Utah vs. Oregon State, 1970 October 10; 16mm film (Reel 106-107)
    Reels 4-5, 5-5
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1970 October 17; 16mm film (Reel 108-112)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1970 October 17; 16mm film (Reel 113-114)
- Coach's films: games, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1970 October 17; 16mm film (Reel 115-117)
  - Utah vs. Arizona, 1970 October 24; 16mm film (Reel 118-121)
  - Utah vs. Arizona offense, 1970 October 24; 16mm film (Reel 122)
  - Utah vs. Arizona defense, 1970 October 24; 16mm film (Reel 123-124)
  - Utah vs. San Jose State defense, 1970 October 31; 16mm film (Reel 125-126)
  - Utah vs. San Jose State, 1970 October 31; 16mm film (Reel 127)
    Reel 4-4
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1970 November 07; 16mm film (Reel 128-130)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1970 November 07; 16mm film (Reel 131-132)
  - Utah vs. BYU freshman game, 1970 November 13; 8mm film (Reel 133-134)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1970 November 14; 16mm film (Reel 135)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1970 November 21; 16mm film (Reel 136)
- Coach's films: games, 1971 (Box 7)
  - University of Utah first spring scrimmage, 1971; 8mm film (Reel 137)
  - University of Utah second spring scrimmage, 1971 April 17; 8mm film (Reel 138-139)
  - University of Utah first spring game, 1971 April 24; 16mm film (Reel 140)
  - University of Utah second spring game, 1971 May 01; 16mm film (Reel 141-142)
    Reels 1-4, 2-4
  - University of Utah first fall scrimmage, 1971 September 04; 8mm film (Reel 143-144)
  - University of Utah second fall scrimmage, 1971 September 11; 16mm film (Reel 145)
    Reel 2
  - Utah vs. Mesa Junior College freshman game offense, 1971 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 146-147)
  - Utah vs. Utah State freshman game, 1971; 16mm film (Reel 148)
  - Utah vs. Oregon defense, 1971 September 18; 16mm film (Reel 149-150)
  - Utah vs. Oregon offense, 1971 September 18; 16mm film (Reel 151)
  - Utah vs. Oregon, 1971 September 18; 16mm film (Reel 152-156)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State, 1971 September 25; 16mm film (Reel 157)
  - Utah vs. Washington State, 1971 October 02; 16mm film (Reel 158-161)
    Reels 1-5, 2-5, 3-5, 4-5
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1971 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 162)
- Coach's films: games, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1971 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 163)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1971 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 164-165)
  - Utah vs. UTEP black and white cut footage, 1971 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 166)
  - Utah vs. UTEP color, 1971 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 167-169)
    Reels 1-4, 2-4, 3-4
  - Utah vs. Colorado State, 1971 October 16; 16mm film (Reel 170-173)
  - Utah vs. Arizona, 1971 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 174-177)
  - Utah vs. Arizona defense, 1971 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 178-179)
    Reels 1-1, 1-2
  - Utah vs. Arizona offense, 1971 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 180-181)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1971 October 30; 16mm film (Reel 182-185)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1971 October 30; 16mm film (Reel 186-187)
- Coach's films: games, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1971 October 30; 16mm film (Reel 188)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1971 October 30; 16mm film (Reel 189-190)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1971 November 06; 16mm film (Reel 191-192)
    Reels 1-3, 3-3
  - Utah vs. New Mexico black and white, 1971 November 06; 16mm film (Reel 193-195)
    Reels 1-5, 3-5, 5-5
  - Utah vs. New Mexico color, 1971 November 06; 16mm film (Reel 196-200)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1971 November 13; 16mm film (Reel 201)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1971 November 13; 16mm film (Reel 202-203)
    Reels 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1971 November 13; 16mm film (Reel 204-206)
    Reels 1-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. BYU, 1971 November 20; 16mm film (Reel 207)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1971 November 20; 16mm film (Reel 208)
  - Unidentified football reels, 1971; 16mm film (Reel 209-210)
- Coach's films: games, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Utah vs. University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), 1973 October 06; 16mm film (Reel 211)
    Reel 3-4
  - University of Utah varsity scrimmage, 1974 September 07; 16mm film (Reel 212-213)
  - University of Utah passing, 1974 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 214)
  - University of Utah passing: one on one pass skeleton, 1974 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 215)
  - University of Utah passing: backs on c's, 1974 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 216)
  - Spring football: green and blue, 1974 April 27; 16mm film (Reel 217)
  - Spring football: red and gold, 1974 April 27; 16mm film (Reel 218)
  - University of Utah spring game, 1974; 16mm film (Reel 219-220)
  - Spring football: option, one on one pass, 1974 April 24; 16mm film (Reel 221)
  - Spring football: three on three, five on five, backs on ends, 1974 April 24; 16mm film (Reel 222)
  - Special teams "problems" from season, 1974; 16mm film (Reel 223)
  - Kick-off onside kick, 1974; 16mm film (Reel 224)
  - Utah vs. Rice kicking, 1974; 16mm film (Reel 225)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1974 September 21; 16mm film (Reel 226-229)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1974 September 21; 16mm film (Reel 230-233)
    Two sets of two: reels 1-2, 1-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1974 September 21; 16mm film (Reel 234)
- Coach's films: games, 1968 (Box 11)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1974 September 21; 16mm film (Reel 235-236)
  - Utah vs. Oregon, 1974 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 237-238)
  - Utah vs. Oregon defense, 1974 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 239-240)
  - Utah vs. Oregon defensive kicking, 1974 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 241)
    Reel 1-1
  - Utah vs. Oregon offensive kicking, 1974 September 28; 16mm film (Reel 242)
  - Utah vs. Arizona, 1974 October 12; 16mm film (Reel 243-246)
  - Utah vs. Arizona defense, 1974 October 12; 16mm film (Reel 247-248)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State, 1974 October 19; 16mm film (Reel 249-250)
    Reels 1 and 3
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, 1974 October 19; 16mm film (Reel 251-253)
    Reels 1-2, 1-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1974 October 26; 16mm film (Reel 254-256)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1974 October 26; 16mm film (Reel 257)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1974 October 26; 16mm film (Reel 258)
- Coach's films: games, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Utah vs. San Jose State, 1974 November 02; 16mm film (Reel 259-262)
  - Utah vs. San Jose State offense, 1974 November 02; 16mm film (Reel 263-264)
  - Utah vs. San Jose State defense, 1974 November 02; 16mm film (Reel 265-266)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1974 November 09; 16mm film (Reel 267-268)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1974 November 09; 16mm film (Reel 269-270)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1974 November 09; 16mm film (Reel 271-274)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1974 November 09; 16mm film (Reel 275)
- Coach's films: spring practice, 1975 (Box 13)
  - University of Utah spring football, 1975 May 03; 16mm film (Reel 276-278)
  - University of Utah spring football, 1975 May 07; 16mm film (Reel 279-281)
  - 44 spring pass skeleton, 1975 April 30; 16mm film (Reel 282)
  - University of Utah spring football, 1975 April 19; 16mm film (Reel 283-285)
  - Scrimmage, pass protection, pass skeleton, drills, 1975 April 12; 16mm film (Reel 286-289)
  - Season highlights, 1975; 16mm film (Reel 290)
  - Kicking game, 1975 August 28; 1975 August 30; 16mm film (Reel 291)
  - Scrimmage, 1975 September 03; 16mm film (Reel 292-294)
  - Scrimmage, 1975 September 06; 16mm film (Reel 295-296)
  - University of Utah junior varsity game, 1975 September 12; 16mm film (Reel 297-298)
- Coach's films: games, 1975 (Box 14)
  - University of Utah junior varsity game, 1975 September 12; 16mm film (Reel 299-300)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1975 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 301-304)
    Two copies each of reels 1-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1975 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 3-5-307)
    Reels 1-1, 1-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1975 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 308)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1975 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 309)
  - Utah vs. Washington State kicking, 1975 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 308)
  - Utah vs. Washington State offense, 1975 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 309-310)
  - Utah vs. Washington State defense, 1975 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 311)
  - Utah vs. Washington State, 1975 September 13; 16mm film (Reel 312)
  - Utah vs. Indiana, 1975 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 313-316)
  - Utah vs. Indiana; Iowa State vs. UCLA, 1975 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 317)
  - Utah vs. Indiana offense, 1975 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 318-320)
- Coach's films: games, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Utah vs. Indiana defense, 1975 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 321-323)
  - Utah vs. Indiana kicking, 1975 September 27; 16mm film (Reel 324)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State, 1975 October 04; 16mm film (Reel 325-328)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State kicking, 1975 October 04; 16mm film (Reel 329)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State defense, 1975 October 04; 16mm film (Reel 330-332)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State offense, 1975 October 04; 16mm film (Reel 333-336)
    Reels 1-2, 1-2, 2-2, 2-2
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1975 October 11; 16mm film (Reel 337-338)
    Reels 2-4, 4-4
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1975 October 11; 16mm film (Reel 339)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1975 October 11; 16mm film (Reel 340)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico offense, 1975 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 341-344)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1975 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 345-346)
- Coach's films: games, 1975 (Box 16)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defense, 1975 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 347-348)
    Reels 1-2, 1-2
  - Utah vs. New Mexico kicking, 1975 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 349)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico, 1975 October 18; 16mm film (Reel 351-353)
  - Utah vs. Oregon, 1975 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 354-357)
  - Utah vs. Oregon offense, 1975 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 358-361)
  - Utah vs. Oregon defense, 1975 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 362-363)
  - Utah vs. Oregon kicking, 1975 October 25; 16mm film (Reel 364)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1975 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 365-367)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, 1975 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 368-370)
- Coach's films: games, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, 1975 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 371)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State kicking, 1975 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 372)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State, 1975 November 01; 16mm film (Reel 373)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee, 1975 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 374-377)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee defense, 1975 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 378-379)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee offense, 1975 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 380)
  - Utah vs. Tennessee kicking, 1975 November 08; 16mm film (Reel 381)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1975 November 15; 16mm film (Reel 382-385)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1975 November 15; 16mm film (Reel 386-389)
  - Utah vs. BYU kicking, 1975 November 15; 16mm film (Reel 390)
  - Utah vs. Arizona, 1975 November 22; 16mm film (Reel 391-393)
- Coach's films: spring and fall practice, 1976 (Box 18)
  - University of Utah spring football drills: guards, 1976; 16mm film (Reel 394)
  - University of Utah spring football drills: tight ends, 1976; 16mm film (Reel 395)
  - University of Utah spring football drills: tackles, 1976; 16mm film (Reel 396)
  - University of Utah spring football drills: centers, 1976; 16mm film (Reel 397)
  - University of Utah spring football goal line, 1976 April 20; 16mm film (Reel 398)
  - University of Utah spring football goal line, skeleton, 1976 April 27; 16mm film (Reel 399)
  - University of Utah spring football teamwork, skeleton, 1976 April 27; 16mm film (Reel 400)
  - University of Utah fall drills: D-line, 1976 September 01; 16mm film (Reel 401)
  - University of Utah fall drills: 7 on 7, 1976 September 01; 16mm film (Reel 402)
  - University of Utah fall drills: linebackers, 1976 September 01; 16mm film (Reel 403)
  - University of Utah fall drills: pass skeleton, 1976 September 01; 16mm film (Reel 404)
  - University of Utah fall skeleton, 1976 September 04; 16mm film (Reel 405)
  - University of Utah fall scrimmage, 1976 September 04; 16mm film (Reel 406)
  - University of Utah fall pass rush, 1976 September 04; 16mm film (Reel 407)
  - University of Utah fall fullback drill, 1976 September 07; 16mm film (Reel 408)
  - University of Utah fall pass skeleton, 1976 September 07; 16mm film (Reel 409)
  - University of Utah fall scrimmage, 1976 September 07; 16mm film (Reel 410)
  - Utah vs. Rice Thursday practice offense, 1976 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 411)
  - Utah vs. Rice Thursday practice defense, 1976 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 412)
  - Utah vs. Rice Thursday practice kicking, 1976 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 413)
  - Utah vs. Rice Thursday practice offense, 1976 September 10; 16mm film (Reel 411)
  - Utah offense, 1976 September 23; 16mm film (Reel 412)
  - Utah vs. UTEP Thursday practice offense, 1976 September 30; 16mm film (Reel 413)
  - Utah vs. UTEP Thursday practice defense, 1976 September 30; 16mm film (Reel 414)
- Coach's films: Thursday practice, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State Thursday practice offense, 1976 October 07; 16mm film (Reel 415)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State Thursday practice defense, 1976 October 07; 16mm film (Reel 416)
  - Utah vs. Utah State Thursday practice offense, 1976 October 14; 16mm film (Reel 417)
  - Utah vs. Utah State Thursday practice defense, 1976 October 14; 16mm film (Reel 418)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming Thursday practice offense, 1976 October 21; 16mm film (Reel 419)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming Thursday practice defense, 1976 October 21; 16mm film (Reel 420)
  - Utah vs. Arizona Thursday practice offense, 1976 October 28; 16mm film (Reel 421)
  - Utah vs. Arizona Thursday practice defense, 1976 October 28; 16mm film (Reel 422)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico Thursday practice offense, 1976 November 04; 16mm film (Reel 423)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico Thursday practice defense, 1976 November 04; 16mm film (Reel 424)
  - Utah vs. New Mexico defensive kicking, 1976 November 06; 16mm film (Reel 425)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, 1976 November 11; 16mm film (Reel 426)
    Possibly Thursday practice
  - Utah vs. BYU Thursday practice defense, 1976 November 18; 16mm film (Reel 427)
  - Utah vs. Rice, 1976 September 18; 16mm film (Reel 428-431)
  - Utah vs. Rice defense, 1976 September 18; 16mm film (Reel 432-435)
  - Utah vs. Rice offense, 1976 September 18; 16mm film (Reel 436-438)
- Coach's films: games, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Utah vs. Rice offense, 1976 September 18; 16mm film (Reel 439)
  - Utah vs. Oregon, 1976 September 25; 16mm film (Reel 440-443)
  - Utah vs. Oregon offense, 1976 September 25; 16mm film (Reel 444-446)
  - Utah vs. Oregon defense, 1976 September 25; 16mm film (Reel 447-450)
  - Utah vs. UTEP, 1976 October 02; 16mm film (Reel 451-454)
  - Utah vs. UTEP offense, 1976 October 02; 16mm film (Reel 455-458)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1976 October 02; 16mm film (Reel 459-461)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defensive kicking, 1976 October 02; 16mm film (Reel 462)
- Coach's films: games, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Utah vs. UTEP defense, 1976 October 02; 16mm film (Reel 463)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State, 1976 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 464-468)
    Reels 1-4, 2-4, 3-4, 4-4, and 1-?
  - Utah vs. Iowa State defense, 1976 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 469-472)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State offense, 1976 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 473-476)
  - Utah vs. Iowa State kicking, 1976 October 09; 16mm film (Reel 477)
  - Utah vs. Utah State, 1976 October 16; 16mm film (Reel 478-480)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defense, 1976 October 16; 16mm film (Reel 481-484)
  - Utah vs. Utah State defensive kicking, 1976 October 16; 16mm film (Reel 485)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1976 October 16; 16mm film (Reel 486)
- Coach's films: games, 1976 (Box 22)
  - Utah vs. Utah State offense, 1976 October 16; 16mm film (Reel 487-489)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming, 1976 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 490)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming defense, 1976 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 491-492)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming offense, 1976 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 493-495)
  - Utah vs. Wyoming kicking, 1976 October 23; 16mm film (Reel 496)
  - Utah vs. Arizona, 1976 October 30; 16mm film (Reel 497-499)
    Reels 1-4, 3-3, 4-4
  - Utah vs. Arizona offense, 1976 October 30; 16mm film (Reel 500-502)
  - Utah vs. Arizona defense, 1976 October 30; 16mm film (Reel 503-504)
  - Utah vs. Arizona kicking, 1976 October 30; 16mm film (Reel 505)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State offense, 1976 November 13; 16mm film (Reel 506)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1976 November 13; 16mm film (Reel 507)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State kicking, 1976 November 13; 16mm film (Reel 508)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1976 November 20; 16mm film (Reel 509-510)
- Coach's films: games, 1976 (Box 23)
  - Utah vs. BYU offense, 1976 November 20; 16mm film (Reel 511)
  - Utah vs. Louisiana State, 1976 November 27; 16mm film (Reel 512)
  - Utah vs. Louisiana State offense, 1976 November 27; 16mm film (Reel 513-514)
    Reels 1 and 2
- Coach's films: defense, 1977-1980 (Box 24a)
  - Utah vs. Arizona State defense, 1977 October 29; 16mm film (Reel 515-516)
  - Utah vs. Florida defense, 1977 November 19; 16mm film (Reel 517-518)
  - Utah vs. Houston defense, 1978 September 23; 16mm film (Reel 519-520)
  - Utah vs. Iowa defense, 1978 October 06; 16mm film (Reel 521-522)
  - Utah vs. Weber State defense, 1978 October 14; 16mm film (Reel 523-524)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1978 November 18; 16mm film (Reel 525-526)
  - Utah vs. Utah State kicking, 1978 November 25; 16mm film (Reel 527)
  - Utah vs. University of Nevada Las Vegas (UNLV) defense, 1979 October 20; 16mm film (Reel 528)
  - Utah vs. Boise State defense, 1980 September 06; 16mm film (Reel 529-530)
  - Utah vs. UNLV defense, 1980 September 20; 16mm film (Reel 531-532)
  - Utah vs. BYU defense, 1980 November 22; 16mm film (Reel 533-534)